http://www.hootville.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
We guard your privacy jealously.
Hootville Communications respects your privacy and we will do our best to ensure the information you provide to us remains private. You know, just between you and us.
We won’t swap, share or sell your details. We collect minimal personal information required for maintaining data with regards to the transactions of Hootville Communications. We’re much too self-interested to care much about you anyhow.
We collect IP addresses, which is the automatic number assigned to your computer when you surf the web, to allow us to count total number of “hits” on our sites. However, your IP address is not connected to any personally identifiable or on-line contact information like a name and address, so you remain anonymous. We will never discover your online shopping or dating habits. You cad.
We do know who reads our eNewsletter and will be hurt if you fail to read every word and click every link. I mean really, would it kill you?
We may need to disclose your data to appropriate persons where required by law. Our site links to other sites. Hootville Communications is not responsible for the privacy policy of other web sites.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. If we decide to change our privacy policy we will post any changes to this web site so tune in daily.
Hootville Communications reserves the right to change this statement at any time. So there.
Comments are closed.
Copyright © 2010-2011 Hootville Communications, Prahran, Melbourne Australia. Tel 03 9017 1062. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy | Sitemap
